and they've got
this kind of
cool parallax sort
of thing. It
didn't do this
stuff to begin
with, but these
decisions are what
can make you
a good designer
using this AI
stuff. So we
go down here
to blog posts,
and each of
these we've got
this kind of
cool hover thing.
And then we
go down here
to our last
call-daction section. And
obviously, of course,
it's completely responsive
as well. This
all stacks down
just like that.
At the moment,
this is just
one page, but
if you were
building this out
for real, you
would just then
move on to
the next page,
get it to
kind of generate
a structure, and
then you can
fine tune it
just in the
same way. The
good thing is,
once you've done
one page and
you move on
to the next
page, a lot
of the variables,
a lot of
the typography, is
already brought over.
So it's a
little easier to
build on. Everyone
loves to talk
about AI slop.
And if you
look at this
website, we use
a lot of
that sort of
blue and red
and purple and
that whole sort
of thing. It's
very AI, and
we used AI
to build it
completely. But I
hope all you
guys can get
out of this
video is, it's
a tool to
literally get you...