And it is
still looking pretty
good. So let's
scroll down and
then let's get
some of these
other sections filled
into. Now I've
just generated a
few more images
from mid-journey. Then
if we refresh,
we now see
them in our
features area. And
then we could
do the same
for the different
blog posts. So
it's this sort
of workflow here
when you go
into using Cloud
Code and making
all these little
micro adjustments, adding
things and fine
tuning it. Feel
like that's when
you can take
it from a
cloud design into
something you could
actually call your
own. If you
want to improve
your skills as
a designer, or
maybe you're already
a designer and
you want to
future proof your
career being ahead
of these tools,
being able to
use these tools,
you could sign
up to my
upcoming course. You
want to just
put your e-ball
in to show
your interest than
the URL is
here. Okay, so
I've made a
few adjustments from
the original design
and I'll show
you what I've
done here. So
I didn't spend
too much time
on this, but
I changed the
logo out. I
changed the position
of the navigation.
Kind of swapped
the colors a
little bit. And
you know, you
can see we've
still got that
kind of glitchy
thing going on
down there. I
think this is
a really cool
hero. You can
click there to
watch the trailer.
As you scroll
down, we've got
this section here.
And these images
we just made
in mid-journey as
well.