Cloud design has
just been released
by the makers
of Claude. People
are hailing this
as the end
to the need
of web designers.
You know, we
see this every
time there's a
new tool introduced
to the space.
But in today's
video, I want
to try it
out with you
guys and we'll
create something. And
let's see how
good it is.
Okay, so to
try this out,
I believe you
need a Claude
subscription, but I
just have the
most basic one.
We have this
new tab called
design. So we
can see here
on the left
sidebar, we've got
prototype, a wireframe
or a high
fidelity UI, a
slide deck from
a template or
other. So one
of the main
things with Claude
design is they
have a big
focus on setting
up a design
system. So a
design system is
essentially just your
blueprint to your
design language of
your page. So
it'll have stuff
like the brand
colors, what fonts
do you use,
what gradients do
you have strokes,
what thickness, like
all this stuff
that comes together
to create your
sort of brand.
But let's be
honest, most beginner
projects don't have
a design system.
We don't have
a design system
to work with
because this doesn't
exist yet. So
let's just go
and make a
wireframe and we'll
call this game
AI and we'll
choose wireframe. So
you can see
here again, if
you have a
design system, if
screenshot or you
can drag in
a figma file.
Now, if you're
not familiar with
me already, I'm
a web designer.
I've been doing
this for 15
plus years, creating
new eyes from
scratch. Generally, my
process starts at
Figma, but for
the purpose of
this video, I'm
just going to
pretend I've got
zero design knowledge.
And we're going
to see if
we can get
cloud design to
do a lot
of the heavy
lifting. We're going
to give it
this prompt here,
create me a
wireframe.