one click on
subtle upscale and
we're going to
bring that over
into over cloud
design. So we're
going to drag
our image down
here and then
we're going to
say let's use
this as a
full screen hero
image and just
like that it's
added it and
it's even added
these sort of
grid lines across
it which looks
really cool that
kind of sits
on top of
the text as
well and it's
added this sort
of gradient at
the bottom so
this stuff's actually
readable. We've let
cloud designs kind
of do its
thing and then
we'll let mid
journey just kind
of do and
we've chosen the
first things of
each of them
and just put
them together and
that looks pretty
good. Now if
we preview it
in a new
tab we can
scale it down
and see if
it's responsive.