and then we
can click there
could change the
text to this
exactly as you
want. So we've
got a pretty
good starting point,
letting Claude design
do all the
heavy lifting. But
now we're going
to generate some
AI assets to
really bring this
to life. Okay,
so we're going
to head into
mid-journey and I'm
going to give
it this prompt
here for a
cyberpunk female character
on a solid
red background. And
then we'll make
sure that it's
set to 16
by 9. Let
me quickly introduce
today's sponsor, the
video Skillshare. Now
I'm a massive
fan of using
AI to quickly
generate assets for
my designs. But
a great tool
for any designer
to have is
to learn how
to do this
stuff yourself. And
then you can
save time with
AI later. Skillshare
has creative classes
created by world-class
industry leaders, illustrators,
graphic designers, and
entrepreneurs. It is
one of the
best ways to
learn a new
skill or pick
up a new
hobby. If you're
looking for a
way to reconnect
with your creativity,
Skillshare can be
a great way
to do that.
I've been following
along with this
blender course to
incorporate more 3D
work into my
designs because although
you can create
stuff with AI,
being able to
actually create stuff
from the scratch
from the foundation,
I think that's
just going to
help you be
a better designer.
It has so
many courses on
there that are
specifically so valuable
for designers in
this AI world.
The first 500
people to use
the link in
the description or
scan this QR
code, get a
free trial month
for Skillshare. So
if you want
to learn new
skills as a
designer or pick
up a new
hobby, definitely check
out Skillshare. We
can see that
is coming through
just like that.
Now that is
really cool actually.
Well I really
like this...