a cyberpunk type
game, large video
hero with H1
and called action
bottom left. The
game should be
called city punks,
the second section
should be two
features about the
game, then a
news section and
then a big
fool with called
action section to
play the game
and a footer.
So let's run
that. Now we've
just completely made
up this brief
but let's just
say you have
a brief from
an actual client,
you can just
copy and paste
that into Cloud
Design 2. Now
this is what
we get, it's
given us three
different variations so
we've got one
with a left
aligned hero centered,
that's like very
standard sort of
layout and then
we've got one
more like a
split screen thing
so it's like
left and right.
Now this is
where Cloud Design
gets quite interesting
because you can
tweak it down
here. So let's
just say we
want to go
with A and
then nav style
where it says
minimal nav, let's
change that to
full nav and
then you can
see we've got
a navigation up
there. Now let's
say let's go
with A full
style nav and
let's tell it
to develop this
into a high
fidelity UI design.
And this is
what it gives
us so this
is looking pretty
good actually. We've
got this little
glitch effect on
the H1, quite
cool.