and all the
sections now work
on mobile a
lot better. So
we've created this
fully responsive website
using cloud design
in a matter
of minutes. We've
made it generate
a wireframe, it's
turned that wireframe
into full high
fidelity website and
then we pulled
in assets and
we'd pretty much
just one-shot it
each thing along
the way. And
if you have
no technical design
knowledge, this is
pretty good. One
of the biggest
downsides with cloud
design right now
is it uses
up a lot
of usage. We
just used about
50% of that
of our weekly
limit. So now
we actually can't
technically take this
further on our
plan that we
have right now.
But what we
can do is
we can go
up here and
we can do
hand off to
cloud code. And
we're gonna copy
this command here.
And we're gonna
paste this into
cloud code so
we could start
using our cloud
code usage instead
of our cloud
design usage. So
now cloud code's
done its thing.
We have a
local version of
our site and
I've just got
it open here
in Chrome. And
then on the
right, I have
a terminal version
of cloud code.
And then this
is what I'm
gonna use to
make further edits
to really refine
this. Now let's
go back into
mid-journey here and
let's animate our
image and we'll
turn that into
a background video.
So let's try
this. We'll keep
it as a
loop.